[
    
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"If x = 2k – 1 and y = k is a solution of the equation 3x – 5y – 7 = 0, find the value of k.",
        "options":
        [
            "k = 12",
            "k = 10",
            "k = 8",
            "k = 9"
        ],
        "correctAns": "k = 10"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"If x = 2a + 1 and y = a – 1 is a solution of the equation 2x – 3y + 5 = 0, find the value of a.",
        "options":
        [
            "a = -10",
            "a = 10",
            "a = 8",
            "a = 9"
        ],
        "correctAns": "a = -10"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"Find the value of k, if x = 1, y = 1 is a solution of the equation 2x + 3y = k.",
        "options":
        [
            "k = 3",
            "k = 6",
            "k = 5",
            "k = 4"
        ],
        "correctAns": "k = 5"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"Find the value of k, if x = - k and y = 5/2 is a solution of the equation x + 4y – 7 = 0.",
        "options":
        [
            "k = -2",
            "k = 4",
            "k = 3",
            "k = 2"
        ],
        "correctAns": "k = 3"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"If x = -1, y = 2 is a solution of the equation 3x + 4y = k, find the value of k.",
        "options":
        [
            "k = 5",
            "k = 8",
            "k = 3",
            "k = 7"
        ],
        "correctAns": "k = 5"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"The distance between the graph of the equations x = -3 and x = 2 is",
        "options":
        [
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
            "5"
        ],
        "correctAns": "5"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"The graph of the linear equation 2x – y = 4 cuts x-axis at",
        "options":
        [
            "(2, 0)",
            "(-2, 0)",
            "(0, -4)",
            "(0, 4)"
        ],
        "correctAns": "(2, 0)"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"The distance between the graphs of the equations y = -1 and y = 3 is",
        "options":
        [
            "2",
            "4",
            "3",
            "1"
        ],
        "correctAns": "4"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"The equation x – 2 = 0 on number line is represented by",
        "options":
        [
            "A line",
            "A point",
            "Infinitely many lines",
            "Two lines"
        ],
        "correctAns": "A point"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"x = 2, y = -1 is a solution of the linear equation",
        "options":
        [
            "x + 2y = 0",
            "x + 2y = 4",
            "2x + y = 0",
            "2x + y = 5"
        ],
        "correctAns": "x + 2y = 0"
    }
]